11os.com 2017-12-27

# Eleven – Privacy Policy

### Eleven Wireless Inc Privacy Policy Covers:

This policy covers how Eleven Wireless Inc. (“We” or the “Company”) treats personal information that it collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, and/or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that the Company does not own or control, or to people that the Company does not employ or closely manage.

### Information Collection and General Use

The Company collects personal information when you register with the Company, when you use the Company products or services, when you visit the Company pages or the pages of certain the Company partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. The Company may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. If we offer financial products and services, we may also ask for your address, Social Security number, and information about your assets. Once you register with the Company and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

The Company collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we could offer.

The Company automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, MAC address, cookie information, and the page you request.

The Company may use information it collects for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

### Children

This Web site is not to be used by any child under age 13.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

The Company does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with the Company under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help the Company communicate with you about offers from the Company and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Company’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if the Company is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, the Company will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

The Company may display targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria – for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.

The Company does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

The Company advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies).

### Cookies

The Company may set and access cookies on your computer.

The Company may let other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to the cookies.

The Company may use web beacons to access the Company cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with the Company products and services.

### Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and General Preferences

You can edit your Company account information, including your marketing preferences, at any time by contacting the Company.

Users who contact the Company can opt out of receiving future marketing communications or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.

Certain communications from the Company, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Company Newsletter, are considered part of the Company membership and you may not opt out of receiving them.

You can delete your the Company account by contacting the Company.

### Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, & procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you.  
Your Company Account Information is password-protected.  
In certain areas the Company uses industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

The Company may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Company account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

### Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at:

Eleven Software, Inc.  
315 SW 11th Ave, Third Floor  
Portland, OR 97205  
(503) 222.4321
